ILR School Extension Division Additional Records /4063
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Extension Division Additional Records
1954-1971
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4063
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3085501
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 15, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 26, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3065: ILR School Extension Division Records
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Extension and Public Service Division.
3085501
- Discussion Leaders Discussion Manual, 1966.; European Corporate Relations by Wayne Hodges, n.d.; ILR Materials, Vol. II - Special Extension Report.; Miscellaneous Summaries, n.d.; Term Papers for ILR 628 (Prof. Hodges); A Case Study in Redundancy by F. Fo (Box 1)
  - Managerial Process Analysis, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ILR Materials Volume 2 Special Extension Report Miscellaneous Summaries, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Scope and Contents
    Bound
  - Wayne Hodges, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Prof. Hodges, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - School Board Negotiations - Preparation and Practice, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Contract Negotiation Preparation and Practice, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Wayne L. Hodges, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - From Jim Huffan, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - News Outlets, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- CU Business Leadership Course for American Airlines by E. Knowlton, 1956?; Term Papers, ILR 694 and ILR 324 (Hodges); Various Seminar Papers, Clippings, Memos; Handbook for Consumer Counselors by Barbara Wertheimer & R. Sell and other misc.. (Box 2)
  - Cornell University Business Leadership Course for American Airlines Program Summary (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Term Paper Course No. 694 Ibrahim O. Akif (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Guidelines for a Public Relations Program: The Cornell Radio Guild, Inc., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - L.D. Kimborough ILR 628 May 1963 Communications Problem Seminar (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - ILR 490 Term Paper C.S. Lomax, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Communications Program at Amuay Refinery, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - New York Times, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Training the Hardcore, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Prof. Hodges - Master Plan of 1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - New York - Ithaca ILR Collaboration, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Handbook for Consumer Counselors, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Supervisory Development - A Source Book of Conceptual and Action Training Materials (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - IBM, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Conferences on Educational Methods, 1955; Hospital Institute, 1955; Labor Newspaper Writers Conf., 1955; Conf. on Labor Participation in Community Affairs; The Local Union Paper In ILR; Machinists; Buffalo IAM Inst.; LAM Editors of Union Papers; USA Conf. (Box 3)
  - Conferences for IBEW-AFL, Local 3, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Hospital Institute - 1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Conf. on Labor Participation in Comm. Affairs, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Machinists, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Buffalo IAM Institute, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - IAM Editors of Union Papers, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - USA Conference on Mental Health - Spring, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Training Specialists 1955 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Union Middle Management, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Labors News Writers Conf. - 1955 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Conference on Educational Methods for Union Officer and Staff July 25-30, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Conference for CIO Community Services Committee, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Conference of UAW-CIO, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Follow-up Questionnaires, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Worker's Education Conf. at Penn State - 1955 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Extension Teachers' Conference 1954 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Conference of IBEW-AFL, Local 3, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Conf. on Labor Relations and Arbitration- 1954 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Dept. Store Personnel Policies Conf., 1954 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Conference of N.Y.S. Federation of Labor August 3-6, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - G.L.F. Conference - 1954 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - United Gas, Coke and Chem. Workers Conf. -1954 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Conference of IAM-AFL, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - State Univ. Public Relations Conf., 1954 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Public Relations Officers Conf., 1954 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Public Relations Officers Conf. 1954 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Conference of United Steelworkers of America, CIO, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - UAW-CIO Conference, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Training Directors' Conference- 1954 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Conf for Training Specialists - 1954 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Conf. for Training Specialists - 1954 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Conference of UAW-CIO, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Conference UAW-CIO, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Steward Training, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 34)